searchmarketingstandard.com 2013-11-26

# Privacy Policy | iNET Interactive

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which iNET Interactive collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of any of the websites within the iNET Interactive network (the “Websites”). 

**Privacy**  
iNET Interactive is committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to iNET Interactive and believes every User should know how iNET Interactive utilizes the information collected from the Websites. This Websites is not directed at children under 13 years of age. 

**The Information We Collect**  
iNET Interactive may collect personally identifiable information (including demographic and biographic information, business affiliations, and survey responses) from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. Information gathered from each of the Websites will be combined and stored in a single central source. iNET Interactive may also collect information about how Users use our Websites, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Websites, or the domains from which Users originate. We may use “cookies” to track how Users use our Websites. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users’ PC and use to identify the User should they visit the web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Websites. We currently use third party ad software to serve ads on our site. The cookies received with banner ads served by this software is used to collect and build anonymous behavioral profiles by these companies to deliver targeted ads and tracking referrals. 

**How We Use Information**  
iNET Interactive and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors, and business partners may use personally identifiable information collected through the Websites to contact Users regarding products and services, and otherwise to enhance Users’ experience with iNET Interactive and such affiliates, independent contractors, and business partners. iNET Interactive may also use information collected through our Websites for research regarding the effectiveness of the Websites and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of iNET Interactive, its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. 

**Disclosure of Information**  
iNET Interactive may disclose information collected from Users to trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined above. We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. Finally, we may transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of iNET Interactive’s business.

iNET Interactive also reserves the right to disclose information if: (1) the disclosure is necessary or useful to our provision of services; (2) we believe in good faith the disclosure is required by law (such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order); (3) we believe in good faith the disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, interests, or property; or (4) we are acting in good faith to protect an individual’s personal safety.

**Maintenance of Information**  
We utilize industry standard information technology security to keep Users’ information secure. We also attempt to have privacy protection controls in place with our vendors in order to ensure that Users’ personal information is protected from unauthorized access or disclosure. All of our employees must abide by our Privacy Policy. Only authorized employees are permitted to access Users’ personally identifiable information. If an employee violates our privacy policies, he or she will be subject to our disciplinary action, up to and including termination. Nevertheless, iNET Interactive cannot guarantee that Users’ information will be completely secure.

**Updating Your Information**  
It is important that we keep only the most accurate, up-to-date information about you in our records. Therefore, if you believe that our records contain information that needs to be updated, you can email us at privacy@inetinteractive.com to correct or update your contact information. You may also email us at privacy@inetinteractive.com to remove your name, telephone and fax numbers, and postal and email addresses from lists that we maintain for purposes of sending out notices or updates or to request that we refrain from disclosing your personally-identifiable information to third parties.

**Children’s Privacy**  
iNET Interactive is not designed to attract individuals under the age of 18. In accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we do not collect or store any personal information, even in aggregate, about children under the age of 13. If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe that iNET Interactive has any information from or about anyone under the age of 13, please contact us at the contact points specified below.

**Interest-based Advertising**  
iNET Interactive uses advanced ad serving technology to offer interest-based advertising. This platform uses unique cookies to identify and collect data such as web browser type, browsing habits etc. and to store that data for advertising purposes, including interest-based advertising. The data we collect with this targeting is considered non-personally identifiable information (Non-PII). Non-PII data is information that cannot be used to identify, contact or locate a particular individual or entity. We use this data in order to deliver you more relevant advertising and to enhance your experience. We also offer a method for you to opt-out of this advanced targeting by clicking the button below.  

**Privacy Policy Revisions**  
iNET Interactive reserves the right to periodically revise this policy. In the event we modify our policy, we will give reasonable notice of the change on our home page. Since notice of any such policy change will not appear on our website indefinitely and may only be posted for a limited time, it will be incumbent upon you to check our Privacy Policy regularly to see if we have made any modifications. 

**Questions**  
Users may direct questions concerning this Privacy Policy by email to privacy@inetinteractive.com. 

(Adopted September 18, 2012)
